Columbia Pictures stills and key books LSC.2213
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1. Large files
  - GAME IS OVER, THE (US release title), (1966) (Box 282)
  - GENE KRUPA STORY, THE, (1959) (Box 138)
  - GENE KRUPA STORY, THE, (1959) (Box 250)
  - GENE KRUPA STORY, THE, (1959) (Box 251)
  - GENGHIS KHAN, (1965) (Box 16)
  - GENGHIS KHAN, (1965) (Box 422)
  - GEORGY GIRL, (1966) (Box 51)
  - GEORGY GIRL, (1966) (Box 249)
  - GEORGY GIRL, (1966) (Box 250)
  - GEORGY GIRL, (1966) (Box 512)
  - GETTING STRAIGHT, (1970) (Box 124)
  - GIANT CLAW, THE, (1957) (Box 77)
  - GIDEON'S DAY, (1958) (Box 10)
  - GIDGET, (1959) (Box 384)
  - GIDGET GOES HAWAIIAN, (1961) (Box 15)
  - GIDGET GOES HAWAIIAN, (1961) (Box 415)
  - GIDGET GOES TO ROME, (1963) (Box 11)
  - GIDGET GOES TO ROME, (1963) (Box 385)
  - GIDGET GOES TO ROME, (1963) (Box 493)
  - GIFT OF LOVE, (1958) (Box 153)
  - GLASS HOUSES (folder titled GLASS HOUSE), (1972) (Box 124)
  - GO-BETWEEN. THE, (1970) (Box 19)
  - GODDESS, THE, (1958) (Box 71)
  - GODDESS, THE, (1958) (Box 243)
  - GODSPELL, (1973) (Box 12)
  - GODSPELL, (1973) (Box 351)
  - GOING STEADY, (1958) (Box 51)
  - GOLD!, (1974) (Box 400)
  - GOLD!, (1974) (Box 500)
  - GOLDEN FISH, THE, (1959) (Box 255)
  - GOLDEN VOYAGE OF SINBAD, THE, (1974) (Box 402)
  - GOOD DAY FOR A HANGING, (1959) (Box 104)
  - GOOD NEIGHBOR SAM, (1964) (Box 14)
  - GOOD NEIGHBOR SAM, (1964) (Box 388)
  - GOOD NEIGHBOR SAM, (1964) (Box 511)
  - GOOD TIMES, (1967) (Box 100)
  - GOOD TIMES, (1967) (Box 222)
  - GORGON, THE, (1964) (Box 246)
  - Grant, Kathryn / OPERATION MAD BALL, (1957) (Box 99)
  - GRAVY TRAIN, THE, (1974) (Box 346)
  - GRAVY TRAIN, THE, (1974) (Box 407)
  - GRAVY TRAIN, THE, (1974) (Box 549)
  - GREENGAGE SUMMER, THE (folder titled LOSS OF INNOCENCE), (1961) (Box 248)
  - GREENGAGE SUMMER, THE (folder titled LOSS OF INNOCENCE), (1961) (Box 249)
  - GUESS WHO'S COMING TO DINNER?, (1967) (Box 313)
  - GUMSHOE, (1971) (Box 4)
  - GUMSHOE, (1971) (Box 456)
  - GUNMAN'S WALK, (1958) (Box 91)
  - GUNMEN FROM LAREDO, (1959) (Box 94)
  - GUNS OF NAVARONE, THE, (1961) (Box 24)
  - GUNS OF NAVARONE, THE, (1961) (Box 25)
  - GUNS OF NAVARONE, THE, (1961) (Box 202)
  - GUNS OF NAVARONE, THE, (1961) (Box 203)
  - GUNS OF NAVARONE, THE, (1961) (Box 204)
  - GUNS OF NAVARONE, THE, (1961) (Box 463)
  - H.M.S. DEFIANT, (1962) (Box 67)
  - HAMLET, (1969) (Box 64)
  - HAMLET, (1969) (Box 352)
  - HAMMERHEAD, (1968) (Box 9)
  - HAMMERHEAD, (1968) (Box 353)
  - HAND IN HAND, (1960) (Box 63)
  - HAND IN HAND, (1960) (Box 433)
  - HAPPENING, THE, (1967) (Box 320)
  - HAPPENING, THE, (1967) (Box 321)
  - HAPPY BIRTHDAY, WANDA JUNE, (1971) (Box 81)
  - HAPPY BIRTHDAY, WANDA JUNE, (1971) (Box 354)
  - HARD MAN, THE, (1957) (Box 117)
  - HARVEY MIDDLEMEN, FIREMAN, (1965) (Box 418)
  - HAVE ROCKET, WILL TRAVEL, (1959) (Box 69)
  - HEAD, (1968) (Box 10)
  - HEAD, (1968) (Box 324)
  - HEAD, (1968) (Box 325)
  - HELL IS A CITY, (1960) (Box 133)
  - HELL IS A CITY, (1960) (Box 240)
  - HELL IS A CITY, (1960) (Box 241)
  - HELLIONS, THE, (1961) (Box 116)
  - HEROES OF TELEMARK, THE, (1965) (Box 42)
  - HEROES OF TELEMARK, THE, (1965) (Box 442)
  - HEY BOY! HEY GIRL!, (1959) (Box 39)
  - HEY THERE, IT'S YOGI BEAR, (1964) (Box 137)
  - HEY THERE, IT'S YOGI BEAR, (1964) (Box 227)
  - HIGH FLIGHT, (1957) (Box 92)
  - HIGH POWERED RIFLE, THE, (1960) (Box 11)
  - HIRELING, THE, (1973) (Box 355)
  - HOLIDAY FOR LOVERS, (1959) (Box 31)
  - Holliday, Judy, (1951) (Box 74)
  - HOMICIDAL, (1961) (Box 63)
  - HOMICIDAL, (1961) (Box 443)
  - HOOK, LINE AND SINKER, (1969) (Box 14)
  - HOOK, LINE AND SINKER, (1969) (Box 413)
  - HORSEMEN, THE, (1971) (Box 32)
  - HORSEMEN, THE, (1971) (Box 355)
  - HOW TO MURDER A RICH UNCLE (folder titled UNCLE GEORGE), (1957) (Box 82)
  - HOW TO MURDER A RICH UNCLE (folder titled UNCLE GEORGE), (1957) (Box 267)
  - HOW TO SAVE A MARRIAGE -- AND RUIN YOUR LIFE, (1968) (Box 184)
  - HOW TO SAVE A MARRIAGE -- AND RUIN YOUR LIFE (listed as BAND OF GOLD), (1968) (Box 132)
  - HOW TO SAVE A MARRIAGE-- AND RUIN YOUR LIFE, (1968) (Box 185)
  - HUSBANDS, (1970) (Box 118)
  - HUSBANDS, (1970) (Box 355)
  - HUSTLER, THE, (1961) (Box 144)
  - I AIM AT THE STARS, (1960) (Box 56)
  - I AIM AT THE STARS, (1960) (Box 286)
  - I AIM AT THE STARS, (1960) (Box 288)
  - I AIM AT THE STARS, (1960) (Box 524)
  - I NEVER SANG FOR MY FATHER, (1970) (Box 83)
  - I NEVER SANG FOR MY FATHER, (1970) (Box 355)
  - IDOL ON PARADE (US release title), (1959) (Box 68)
  - IMAGES, (1972) (Box 87)
  - IN COLD BLOOD, (1967) (Box 4)
  - IN COLD BLOOD, (1967) (Box 356)
  - IN COLD BLOOD, (1967) (Box 510)
  - IN THE NICK, (1960) (Box 78)
  - INTERLUDE, (1968) (Box 6)
  - INTERLUDE, (1968) (Box 303)
  - INTERLUDE, (1968) (Box 317)
  - INTERNS, THE, (1962) (Box 86)
  - INTERNS, THE, (1962) (Box 258)
  - INTERNS, THE, (1962) (Box 259)
  - INVESTIGATION OF A CITIZEN ABOVE SUSPICION, (1970) (Box 118)
  - IT CAME FROM BENEATH THE SEA, (1955) (Box 296)
  - IT HAPPENED IN ATHENS (folder titled IT HAPPENS IN ATHENS), (1962) (Box 156)
  - IT HAPPENED TO JANE, (1959) (Box 57)
  - IT'S WHAT'S HAPPENING, (1965) (Box 13)
  - J.W. COOP, (1972) (Box 124)
  - J.W. COOP, (1972) (Box 357)
  - JASON AND THE GOLDEN FLEECE (released as JASON AND THE ARGONAUTS), (1963) (Box 69)
  - JASON AND THE GOLDEN FLEECE (released as JASON AND THE ARGONAUTS), (1963) (Box 572)
  - JEANNE EAGELS, (1957) (Box 170)
  - JEANNE EAGELS, (1957) (Box 171)
  - JEANNE EAGELS, (1957) (Box 186)
  - JEANNE EAGELS, (1957) (Box 187)
  - JOURNEY TO THE CENTER OF THE EARTH, (1959) (Box 151)
  - JUKEBOX RHYTHM, (1959) (Box 54)
  - JUKEBOX RHYTHM, (1959) (Box 257)
  - Keim, Betty Lou / TEENAGE REBEL, (1956) (Box 81)
  - KEY, THE, (1958) (Box 99)
  - KIDCO, (1984) (Box 480)
  - KILL ME QUICK, I'M COLD (US release title), (1967) (Box 101)
  - KILL ME QUICK, I'M COLD (US release title), (1967) (Box 433)
  - KILLER AND 21 MEN, THE (aka THE PARSON AND THE OUTLAW), (1957) (Box 123)
  - KILLERS OF KILIMANJARO, (1959) (Box 66)
  - KING OF COMEDY, (1983) (Box 490)
  - KING OF MARVIN GARDENS, THE, (1972) (Box 48)
  - KING OF MARVIN GARDENS, THE, (1972) (Box 358)
  - KING OF MARVIN GARDENS, THE, (1972) (Box 359)
  - KING RAT, (1965) (Box 11)
  - KING RAT, (1965) (Box 359)
  - KING RAT, (1965) (Box 360)
  - KING RAT, (1965) (Box 525)
  - KISS THE GIRLS AND MAKE THEM DIE (US release title; folder titled KISS THE GIRLS AND MAKE THEM CRY), (1966) (Box 139)
  - LADY IN A CAR WITH GLASSES AND A GUN, THE, (1970) (Box 59)
  - LADY IN A CAR WITH GLASSES AND A GUN, THE, (1970) (Box 443)
  - LAND RAIDERS (folder titled THE DAY OF THE LAND GRABBER), (1969) (Box 111)
  - LAST ANGRY MAN, THE, (1959) (Box 282)
  - LAST BLITZKRIEG, THE, (1959) (Box 74)
  - LAST BLITZKRIEG, THE, (1959) (Box 235)
  - LAST HURRAH, THE, (1958) (Box 181)
  - LAST OF THE RENEGADES, (1964) (Box 321)
  - LAST OF THE RENEGADES, (1964) (Box 321)
  - LAST PICTURE SHOW, THE, (1971) (Box 465)
  - LAST REBEL, THE, (1972) (Box 8)
  - LAW AND DISORDER, (1974) (Box 401)
  - LAW AND DISORDER, (1974) (Box 461)
  - LAW AND DISORDER, (1974) (Box 495)
  - LEFT HAND OF GOD, (1955) (Box 145)
  - LEGEND OF TOM DOOLEY, THE, (1959) (Box 72)
  - LET NO MAN WRITE MY EPITAPH, (1960) (Box 268)
  - LET NO MAN WRITE MY EPITAPH (folder titled REACH FOR TOMORROW), (1960) (Box 79)
  - LET THE GOOD TIMES ROLL, (1973) (Box 44)
  - LET THE GOOD TIMES ROLL, (1973) (Box 360)
  - LET THE GOOD TIMES ROLL, (1973) (Box 361)
  - LET'S ROCK, (1958) (Box 77)
  - LIBERATION OF L.B. JONES, THE, (1970) (Box 58)
  - LIFE AT THE TOP, (1965) (Box 14)
  - LIFE AT THE TOP, (1965) (Box 408)
  - LIFE AT THE TOP, (1965) (Box 524)
  - LIFE AT THE TOP, (1965) (Box 537)
  - LILITH, (1964) (Box 9)
  - LILITH, (1964) (Box 416)
  - LINEUP, THE, (1958) (Box 105)
  - LINEUP, THE, (1958) (Box 290)
  - LITTLE BIG MAN, (1970) (Box 404)
  - LITTLE SAVAGE, THE, (1959) (Box 22)
  - LITTLE SAVAGE, THE, (1959) (Box 25)
  - LIVING FREE, (1972) (Box 18)
  - LOCK UP YOUR DAUGHTERS!, (1969) (Box 5)
  - LOCK UP YOUR DAUGHTERS!, (1969) (Box 423)
  - LONG HAUL, THE, (1957) (Box 85)
  - LONG SHIPS, THE, (1964) (Box 298)
  - LOOKING GLASS WAR, THE, (1969) (Box 63)
  - LOOKING GLASS WAR, THE, (1969) (Box 432)
  - LOOKING GLASS WAR, THE, (1969) (Box 550)
  - LORD JIM, (1965) (Box 38)
  - LORD JIM, (1965) (Box 389)
  - LORD JIM, (1965) (Box 509)
  - LOST COMMAND, (1966) (Box 129)
  - LOST COMMAND, (1966) (Box 172)
  - LOST HORIZON, (1973) (Box 3)
  - LOST HORIZON, (1973) (Box 4)
  - LOST HORIZON, (1973) (Box 362)
  - LOST HORIZON, (1973) (Box 363)
  - LOST HORIZON, (1973) (Box 364)
  - LOST HORIZON, (1973) (Box 365)
  - LOST HORIZON, (1973) (Box 366)
  - LOST HORIZON, (1973) (Box 573)
  - LOST IN THE DESERT (US release title; folder titled DIRKIE), (1969) (Box 367)
  - LOST WORLD, (1960) (Box 151)
  - LOST WORLD, (1960) (Box 157)
  - LOVE AND PAIN (AND THE WHOLE DAMN THING), (1973) (Box 47)
  - LOVE AND PAIN (AND THE WHOLE DAMN THING), (1973) (Box 367)
  - LOVE HAS MANY FACES, (1965) (Box 41)
  - LOVE HAS MANY FACES, (1965) (Box 391)
  - LOVE HAS MANY FACES, (1965) (Box 392)
  - LOVE HAS MANY FACES, (1965) (Box 503)
  - LOVE MACHINE, THE, (1971) (Box 24)
  - LOVE MACHINE, THE, (1971) (Box 367)
  - LOVE ME TENDER, (1956) (Box 270)
  - LOVE ON A PILLOW, (1962) (Box 201)
  - LOVE-INS, THE, (1967) (Box 41)
  - LOVE-INS, THE, (1967) (Box 142)
  - LOVE-INS, THE, (1967) (Box 408)
  - LOVING, (1970) (Box 8)
  - LOVING, (1970) (Box 317)
  - LOVING, (1970) (Box 330)
  - L-SHAPED ROOM, THE, (1962) (Box 386)
  - L-SHAPED ROOM, THE, (1962) (Box 504)
  - LUV, (1967) (Box 97)
  - LUV, (1967) (Box 387)
  - LUV, (1967) (Box 498)
  - MACBETH, (1971) (Box 209)
  - MACHINE GUN MCCAIN, (1968) (Box 36)
  - MACKENNA'S GOLD, (1969) (Box 98)
  - MACKENNA'S GOLD, (1969) (Box 148)
  - MACKENNA'S GOLD, (1969) (Box 322)
  - MACKENNA'S GOLD, (1969) (Box 323)
  - MACKENNA'S GOLD, (1969) (Box 324)
  - MACKENNA'S GOLD, (1969) (Box 526)
  - MAD DOG COLL, (1961) (Box 118)
  - MAD DOG COLL, (1961) (Box 304)
  - MAD ROOM, THE, (1969) (Box 102)
  - MAD ROOM, THE, (1969) (Box 368)
  - MAD ROOM, THE, (1969) (Box 369)
  - MADISON AVE., (1962) (Box 21)
  - MAN CALLED FLINTSTONE, THE, (1966) (Box 127)
  - MAN CALLED FLINTSTONE, THE, (1966) (Box 276)
  - MAN CALLED SLEDGE, A, (1970) (Box 130)
  - MAN FOR ALL SEASONS, A, (1966) (Box 7)
  - MAN FOR ALL SEASONS, A, (1966) (Box 44)
  - MAN FOR ALL SEASONS, A, (1966) (Box 352)
  - MAN FROM THE DINERS' CLUB, (1963) (Box 143)
  - MAN FROM THE DINERS' CLUB, THE, (1963) (Box 214)
  - MAN IN THE GRAY FLANNEL SUIT, THE, (1956) (Box 22)
  - MAN IN THE GRAY FLANNEL SUIT, THE, (1956) (Box 30)
  - MAN ON A STRING, (1960) (Box 79)
  - MAN ON A STRING, (1960) (Box 206)
  - MAN ON A STRING, (1960) (Box 207)
  - MAN WITH BOGART'S FACE, THE, (1980) (Box 561)
  - MARINES, LETS GO, (1961) (Box 30)
  - MARINES, LETS GO, (1961) (Box 160)
  - MAROONED, (1969) (Box 24)
  - MAROONED, (1969) (Box 370)
  - MAROONED, (1969) (Box 371)
  - MAROONED, (1969) (Box 539)
  - MAROONED, (1969) (Box 567)
  - MARRIED WOMAN, THE, (1964) (Box 303)
  - Mason, James, (1959) (Box 29)
  - MASTERS OF THE JUNGLE (released in the US as MASTERS OF THE CONGO JUNGLE), (1959) (Box 30)
  - Matthews, Kerwin, (1959) (Box 78)
  - ME AND THE COLONEL, (1958) (Box 301)
  - ME AND THE COLONEL, (1958) (Box 302)
  - MICKEY ONE, (1965) (Box 139)
  - MICKEY ONE, (1965) (Box 217)
  - MIDDLE AGE CRAZY, (1980) (Box 558)
  - MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT, (1959) (Box 233)
  - MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT, (1959) (Box 546)
  - MIDSUMMER NIGHT'S DREAM, A, (1967) (Box 92)
  - MIDSUMMER NIGHT'S DREAM, A, (1967) (Box 305)
  - MIND OF MR. SOAMES, THE, (1970) (Box 8)
  - MIND OF MR. SOAMES, THE, (1970) (Box 371)
  - MIND OF MR. SOAMES, THE, (1970) (Box 551)
  - MISTY, (1961) (Box 160)
  - MODEL SHOP, (1969) (Box 45)
  - MODEL SHOP, (1969) (Box 372)
  - MODEL SHOP, (1969) (Box 505)
  - MONSIEUR VERDOUX, (1947) (Box 507)
  - MOST DANGEROUS MAN ALIVE, THE, (1961) (Box 74)
  - MOUNTAIN ROAD, THE, (1960) (Box 106)
  - MOUNTAIN ROAD, THE, (1960) (Box 177)
  - MOUNTAIN ROAD, THE, (1960) (Box 178)
  - MOUNTAIN ROAD, THE, (1960) (Box 179)
  - MOUSE THAT ROARED, THE, (1959) (Box 283)
  - MR. MOM, (1983) (Box 483)
  - MR. SARDONICUS, (1961) (Box 442)
  - MURDER BY CONTRACT, (1958) (Box 116)
  - MURDERER'S ROW, (1966) (Box 419)
  - MURDERER'S ROW, (1966) (Box 420)
  - MURDERER'S ROW, (1966) (Box 421)
  - MURDERERS' ROW, (1966) (Box 93)
  - Murray, Alena / DESK SET, (1956) (Box 29)
  - MY BODYGUARD, (1980) (Box 557)
  - MY BODYGUARD, (1980) (Box 560)
  - MYSTERIOUS ISLAND, (1961) (Box 465)
  - NAKED EARTH, (1958) (Box 20)
  - NATIONAL HEALTH, OR, NURSE NORTON'S AFFAIR, (1973) (Box 372)
  - NATIONAL HEALTH, OR, NURSE NORTON'S AFFAIR, (1973) (Box 529)
  - NAVY LARK, THE, (1959) (Box 29)
  - NAVY LARK, THE, (1959) (Box 29)
  - NEVER TAKE SWEETS FROM A STRANGER (released as NEVER TAKE CANDY FROM A STRANGER), (1960) (Box 71)
  - NEVER TAKE SWEETS FROM A STRANGER (released as NEVER TAKE CANDY FROM A STRANGER), (1960) (Box 278)
  - NEW CENTURIONS, THE, (1972) (Box 49)
  - NEW CENTURIONS, THE, (1972) (Box 459)
  - NEW CONTRACT PLAYERS, (1954) (Box 90)
  - NEW INTERNS, THE, (1964) (Box 103)
  - NEW INTERNS, THE, (1964) (Box 386)
  - NEW INTERNS, THE, (1964) (Box 502)
  - NICE LITTLE BANK THAT SHOULD BE ROBBED, A, (1958) (Box 154)
  - NICHOLAS AND ALEXANDRA, (1971) (Box 54)
  - NICHOLAS AND ALEXANDRA, (1971) (Box 373)
  - NICHOLAS AND ALEXANDRA, (1971) (Box 451)
  - NICHOLAS AND ALEXANDRA, (1971) (Box 531)
  - NICHOLAS AND ALEXANDRA, (1971) (Box 532)
  - NIGHT IN HEAVEN, A, (1983) (Box 491)
  - NIGHT OF THE GENERALS, THE, (1967) (Box 148)
  - NIGHT THE WORLD EXPLODED, THE, (1957) (Box 207)
  - NO DOWN PAYMENT, (1957) (Box 29)
  - NO DOWN PAYMENT, (1957) (Box 29)
  - NO DOWN PAYMENT, (1957) (Box 159)
  - Norring, Ava, (1951) (Box 23)
  - NORTH TO ALASKA, (1960) (Box 154)
  - NORTH TO ALASKA, (1960) (Box 155)
  - NORTH TO ALASKA (folder titled GO NORTH!), (1960) (Box 158)
  - NORTH TO ALASKA (folder titled GO NORTH!), (1960) (Box 159)
  - NOTHING BUT THE BEST, (1964) (Box 128)
  - NOTHING BUT THE BEST, (1964) (Box 215)
  - NOTORIOUS LANDLADY, THE, (1962) (Box 50)
  - NOTORIOUS LANDLADY, THE, (1962) (Box 102)
  - NOTORIOUS LANDLADY, THE, (1962) (Box 434)
  - NOTORIOUS LANDLADY, THE, (1962) (Box 435)
  - Novak, Kim, (1955) (Box 1)
  - ODESSA FILE, THE, (1974) (Box 394)
  - ODESSA FILE, THE, (1974) (Box 468)
  - ODESSA FILE, THE, (1974) (Box 501)
  - ODESSA FILE, THE, (1974) (Box 501)
  - ODESSA FILE, THE, (1974) (Box 501)
  - ODESSA FILE, THE, (1974) (Box 566)
  - OKLAHOMA CRUDE, (1973) (Box 1)
  - OKLAHOMA CRUDE, (1973) (Box 374)
  - OKLAHOMA CRUDE, (1973) (Box 526)
  - OKLAHOMA CRUDE, (1973) (Box 533)
  - OLD DARK HOUSE, THE, (1963) (Box 8)
  - OLD DARK HOUSE, THE, (1963) (Box 417)
  - OLD DARK HOUSE, THE, (1963) (Box 523)
  - OLIVER!, (1968) (Box 449)
  - OLIVER!, (1968) (Box 450)
  - ON THE WATERFRONT, (1954) (Box 409)
  - ONCE MORE, WITH FEELING, (1960) (Box 195)
  - ONCE MORE, WITH FEELING, (1960) (Box 196)
  - ONCE MORE, WITH FEELING, (1960) (Box 197)
  - ONCE MORE, WITH FEELING, (1960) (Box 198)
  - ONCE MORE, WITH FEELING!, (1960) (Box 68)
  - ONE FOOT IN HELL, (1960) (Box 21)
  - ONLY TWO CAN PLAY, (1962) (Box 94)
  - ONLY TWO CAN PLAY, (1962) (Box 285)
  - ONLY TWO CAN PLAY, (1962) (Box 287)
  - OPEN SEASON, (1974) (Box 393)
  - OPEN SEASON, (1974) (Box 468)
  - OPEN SEASON, (1974) (Box 476)
  - OPEN SEASON, (1974) (Box 476)
  - OPEN SEASON, (1974) (Box 493)
  - OPERATION AMSTERDAM, (1959) (Box 36)
  - OPERATION MAD BALL, (1957) (Box 236)
  - OPERATION MAD BALL, (1957) (Box 237)
  - OPERATION MAD BALL, (1957) (Box 238)
  - OTLEY, (1968) (Box 102)
  - OTLEY, (1968) (Box 429)
  - OUR MAN IN HAVANA, (1959) (Box 45)
  - OUR MAN IN HAVANA, (1959) (Box 289)
  - OUR MAN IN HAVANA, (1959) (Box 293)
  - OUR MAN IN HAVANA, (1959) (Box 294)
  - OUTLAWS IS COMING, THE (folder titled THREE STOOGES MEET THE GUNSLINGERS), (1965) (Box 295)
  - OWL AND THE PUSSYCAT, THE, (1970) (Box 76)
  - OWL AND THE PUSSYCAT, THE, (1970) (Box 509)
  - PAL JOEY, (1957) (Box 208)
  - PAL JOEY, (1957) (Box 518)
  - PATTON, (1970) (Box 145)
  - PAYMENT IN BLOOD (US release title), (1967) (Box 107)
  - PAYMENT IN BLOOD (US release title), (1967) (Box 373)
  - PAYMENT IN BLOOD (US release title), (1967) (Box 534)
  - PENDULUM, (1969) (Box 134)
  - PENDULUM, (1969) (Box 148)
  - PENDULUM, (1969) (Box 262)
  - PENDULUM, (1969) (Box 263)
  - PENDULUM, (1969) (Box 512)
  - PEPE, (1960) (Box 188)
  - PEPE, (1960) (Box 189)
  - PEPE, (1960) (Box 190)
  - PEPE, (1960) (Box 191)
  - PEPE, (1960) (Box 192)
  - PEPE, (1960) (Box 575)
  - PICKUP ALLEY (folder titled INTERPOL), (1957) (Box 232)
  - PICKUP ALLEY (folder titled INTERPOL), (1957) (Box 233)
  - PICNIC, (1955) (Box 173)
  - PICNIC, (1955) (Box 174)
  - PIRATES OF BLOOD RIVER, THE, (1962) (Box 113)
  - PIRATES OF BLOOD RIVER, THE, (1962) (Box 261)
  - PLEASE NOT NOW (US release title), (1961) (Box 32)
  - POPE JOAN, (1972) (Box 53)
  - POPE JOAN, (1972) (Box 424)
  - POPE JOAN, (1972) (Box 425)
  - PORGY AND BESS, (1959) (Box 319)
  - POWER, (1986) (Box 470)
  - POWER, (1986) (Box 477)
  - POWER, (1986) (Box 478)
  - PRIME CUT, (1972) (Box 403)
  - PROFESSIONALS, THE, (1966) (Box 101)
  - PROFESSIONALS, THE, (1966) (Box 403)
  - PSYCHE '59, (1964) (Box 83)
  - PSYCHE '59, (1964) (Box 266)
  - PUMPKIN EATER, THE, (1964) (Box 138)
  - PUMPKIN EATER, THE, (1964) (Box 266)
  - PURPLE HILLS, THE, (1961) (Box 34)
  - PURSUIT OF HAPPINESS, THE, (1971) (Box 103)
  - PURSUIT OF HAPPINESS, THE, (1971) (Box 373)
  - PURSUIT OF HAPPINESS, THE, (1971) (Box 519)
  - PURSUIT OF HAPPINESS, THE, (1971) (Box 527)
  - QUEENS, THE, (1966) (Box 280)
  - QUICK GUN, THE, (1964) (Box 135)
  - QUICK GUN, THE, (1964) (Box 278)
  - R.P.M., (1970) (Box 111)
  - R.P.M., (1970) (Box 430)
  - R.P.M., (1970) (Box 431)
  - RAGE, (1966) (Box 135)
  - RAGE, (1966) (Box 285)
  - RAISIN IN THE SUN, A, (1961) (Box 273)
  - RALLY 'ROUND THE FLAG BOYS!, (1958) (Box 155)
  - REACH FOR GLORY, (1962) (Box 86)
  - REACH FOR GLORY, (1962) (Box 216)
  - RECKONING, THE, (1969) (Box 82)
  - RECKONING, THE, (1969) (Box 112)
  - RECKONING, THE, (1969) (Box 530)
  - REFLECTION OF FEAR, A, (1973) (Box 62)
  - REFLECTION OF FEAR, A, (1973) (Box 527)
  - RELUCTANT SAINT, THE, (1962) (Box 137)
  - RELUCTANT SAINT, THE, (1962) (Box 279)
  - REMARKABLE MR. PENNYMAKER (released as THE REMARKABLE MR. PENNYPACKER), (1959) (Box 33)
  - REMARKABLE MR. PENNYMAKER (released as THE REMARKABLE MR. PENNYPACKER), (1959) (Box 158)
  - REPRISAL!, (1956) (Box 213)
  - REPULSION, (1965) (Box 243)
  - REQUIEM FOR A HEAVYWEIGHT, (1962) (Box 55)
  - REQUIEM FOR A HEAVYWEIGHT, (1962) (Box 206)
  - REQUIEM FOR A HEAVYWEIGHT, (1962) (Box 525)
  - RETURN FROM THE RIVER KWAI, (1989) (Box 578)
  - RICHARD TODD, (1955) (Box 12)
  - RIDE BEYOND VENGEANCE, (1966) (Box 82)
  - RIDE BEYOND VENGEANCE, (1966) (Box 148)
  - RIDE BEYOND VENGEANCE, (1966) (Box 215)
  - RIDE THE WILD SURF, (1964) (Box 74)
  - RIDE THE WILD SURF, (1964) (Box 304)
  - RING-A-DING RHYTHM (folder titled IT'S TRAD, DAD, (1962) (Box 114)
  - RINGS AROUND THE WORLD, (1966) (Box 135)
  - RINGS AROUND THE WORLD, (1966) (Box 176)
  - RIVERRUN, (1971) (Box 97)
  - RIVERRUN, (1970) (Box 240)
  - Robertson, Cliff, (1955) (Box 100)
  - ROBIN AND MARIAN, (1975) (Box 404)
  - ROBIN AND MARIAN, (1975) (Box 405)
  - ROBIN AND MARIAN, (1975) (Box 406)
  - ROBIN AND MARIAN, (1975) (Box 566)
  - RUN WILD, RUN FREE, (1969) (Box 98)
  - RUN WILD, RUN FREE, (1969) (Box 458)
  - RUNNING MAN, THE, (1963) (Box 97)
  - RUNNING MAN, THE, (1963) (Box 279)
  - SAFE AT HOME, (1962) (Box 82)
  - SAFE AT HOME!, (1962) (Box 198)
  - SAFE PLACE, A, (1971) (Box 62)
  - SAFE PLACE, A, (1971) (Box 376)
  - SAFE PLACE, A, (1971) (Box 555)
  - SAIL A CROOKED SHIP, (1961) (Box 94)
  - SAIL A CROOKED SHIP, (1961) (Box 200)
  - SAIL A CROOKED SHIP, (1961) (Box 201)
  - SATURDAY MORNING, (1971) (Box 60)
  - SATURDAY MORNING, (1971) (Box 376)
  - SATURDAY MORNING, (1971) (Box 555)
  - SCREAM OF FEAR, (1961) (Box 77)
  - SCREAM OF FEAR, (1961) (Box 199)
  - SCROOGE, (1970) (Box 404)
  - SECRET OF THE PURPLE REEF, (1960) (Box 34)
  - SEE NO EVIL, (1971) (Box 16)
  - SEE NO EVIL, (1971) (Box 376)
  - SEE NO EVIL, (1971) (Box 548)
  - SEE NO EVIL, HEAR NO EVIL, (1989) (Box 577)
  - SEE NO EVIL, HEAR NO EVIL, (1989) (Box 578)
  - SENIOR PROM, (1958) (Box 56)
  - SEVEN GUNS FOR THE MACGREGORS, (1966) (Box 127)
  - SEVEN GUNS FOR THE MACGREGORS, (1966) (Box 148)
  - SEVEN GUNS FOR THE MACGREGORS, (1966) (Box 244)
  - SEVEN THIEVES, (1960) (Box 21)
  - SEVEN THIEVES, (1960) (Box 145)
  - SEVEN THIEVES, (1960) (Box 146)
  - SEVENTH VOYAGE OF SINBAD, THE, (1958) (Box 199)
  - SEVERED HEAD, A, (1970) (Box 59)
  - SEVERED HEAD, A, (1970) (Box 377)
  - SEVERED HEAD, A, (1970) (Box 548)
  - SEX AND THE TEENAGER (released as TO FIND A MAN), (1972) (Box 61)
  - SEX AND THE TEENAGER (released as TO FIND A MAN), (1972) (Box 377)
  - SHAMUS, (1973) (Box 377)
  - SHAMUS, (1973) (Box 552)
  - SHIP OF FOOLS, (1965) (Box 96)
  - SHIP OF FOOLS, (1965) (Box 328)
  - SHIP OF FOOLS, (1965) (Box 540)
  - SIDDHARTHA, (1972) (Box 377)
  - SIDDHARTHA, (1972) (Box 535)
  - SILENCERS, THE, (1966) (Box 5)
  - SILENCERS, THE, (1966) (Box 452)
  - SILENCERS, THE, (1966) (Box 453)
  - SILENT CALL, THE, (1961) (Box 34)
  - SILENT MOVIE, (1976) (Box 562)
  - SMOKY, (1966) (Box 31)
  - SNORKEL, THE, (1958) (Box 135)
  - SON OF ROBIN HOOD, THE, (1958) (Box 32)
  - SONG WITHOUT END, (1960) (Box 281)
  - SONG WITHOUT END, (1960) (Box 283)
  - SONG WITHOUT END, (1960) (Box 284)
  - SOUTHERN STAR, THE, (1969) (Box 95)
  - SOUTHERN STAR, THE, (1969) (Box 439)
  - SQUAD CAR, (1960) (Box 22)
  - STAND UP AND BE COUNTED, (1972) (Box 63)
  - STAND UP AND BE COUNTED, (1972) (Box 378)
  - STAND UP AND BE COUNTED, (1972) (Box 539)
  - STAR CHAMBER, (1983) (Box 479)
  - STARDUST, (1974) (Box 394)
  - STARDUST, (1974) (Box 468)
  - STARDUST, (1974) (Box 476)
  - STARDUST, (1974) (Box 492)
  - STEPFORD WIVES, THE, (1975) (Box 394)
  - STEPFORD WIVES, THE, (1975) (Box 502)
  - STEPFORD WIVES, THE, (1975) (Box 566)
  - STEPFORD WIVES, THE, (1975) (Box 566)
  - STONE KILLER, THE, (1973) (Box 378)
  - STONE KILLER, THE, (1973) (Box 537)
  - STOP ME BEFORE I KILL! (folder titled THE FULL TREATMENT), (1960) (Box 113)
  - STOP ME BEFORE I KILL! (folder titled THE FULL TREATMENT), (1960) (Box 218)
  - STOP! LOOK! AND LAUGH!, (1960) (Box 218)
  - STORY OF ESTHER COSTELLO, THE, (1957) (Box 318)
  - STORY OF RUTH, THE, (1960) (Box 20)
  - STORY OF RUTH, THE, (1960) (Box 169)
  - STRAIT-JACKET, (1964) (Box 76)
  - STRAIT-JACKET, (1964) (Box 205)
  - STRANGE ONE, THE, (1957) (Box 306)
  - STRANGERS WHEN WE MEET, (1960) (Box 52)
  - STRANGERS WHEN WE MEET, (1960) (Box 185)
  - STRANGERS WHEN WE MEET, (1960) (Box 505)
  - STUDY IN TERROR, A, (1965) (Box 137)
  - STUDY IN TERROR, A, (1965) (Box 219)
  - SUDDENLY LAST SUMMER, (1959) (Box 270)
  - SUDDENLY LAST SUMMER, (1959) (Box 524)
  - SUMMER WISHES, WINTER DREAMS, (1973) (Box 378)
  - SUMMER WISHES, WINTER DREAMS, (1973) (Box 536)
  - SUMMERTREE, (1971) (Box 59)
  - SUMMERTREE, (1971) (Box 379)
  - SUMMERTREE, (1971) (Box 536)
  - SURPRISE PACKAGE, (1960) (Box 131)
  - SURPRISE PACKAGE, (1960) (Box 193)
  - SURPRISE PACKAGE, (1960) (Box 194)
  - SWIMMER, THE, (1968) (Box 379)
  - SWIMMER, THE, (1968) (Box 538)
  - SWORD OF SHERWOOD FOREST, (1960) (Box 73)
  - SWORD OF SHERWOOD FOREST, (1960) (Box 239)
  - SYNANON, (1965) (Box 67)
  - SYNANON, (1965) (Box 148)
  - SYNANON, (1965) (Box 243)
  - SYNANON, (1965) (Box 244)
  - TAKE A GIRL LIKE YOU, (1970) (Box 55)
  - TAKE A GIRL LIKE YOU, (1970) (Box 383)
  - TAKE A GIRL LIKE YOU, (1970) (Box 518)
  - TAKE, THE, (1974) (Box 379)
  - TAKE, THE, (1974) (Box 536)
  - TAMING OF THE SHREW, THE, (1967) (Box 124)
  - TAMING OF THE SHREW, THE, (1967) (Box 441)